var ve=Object.defineProperty;var ye=(t,e,n)=>e in t?ve(t,e,{enumerable:!0,configurable:!0,writable:!0,value:n}):t[e]=n;var V=(t,e,n)=>(ye(t,typeof e!="symbol"?e+"":e,n),n);(function(){const e=document.createElement("link").relList;if(e&&e.supports&&e.supports("modulepreload"))return;for(const o of document.querySelectorAll('link[rel="modulepreload"]'))s(o);new MutationObserver(o=>{for(const a of o)if(a.type==="childList")for(const u of a.addedNodes)u.tagName==="LINK"&&u.rel==="modulepreload"&&s(u)}).observe(document,{childList:!0,subtree:!0});function n(o){const a={};return o.integrity&&(a.integrity=o.integrity),o.referrerPolicy&&(a.referrerPolicy=o.referrerPolicy),o.crossOrigin==="use-credentials"?a.credentials="include":o.crossOrigin==="anonymous"?a.credentials="omit":a.credentials="same-origin",a}function s(o){if(o.ep)return;o.ep=!0;const a=n(o);fetch(o.href,a)}})();function P(){}function pe(t){return t()}function ae(){return Object.create(null)}function B(t){t.forEach(pe)}function Z(t){return typeof t=="function"}function U(t,e){return t!=t?e==e:t!==e||t&&typeof t=="object"||typeof t=="function"}function qe(t){return Object.keys(t).length===0}function b(t,e){t.appendChild(e)}function k(t,e,n){t.insertBefore(e,n||null)}function _(t){t.parentNode&&t.parentNode.removeChild(t)}function ee(t,e){for(let n=0;n<t.length;n+=1)t[n]&&t[n].d(e)}function y(t){return document.createElement(t)}function T(t){return document.createTextNode(t)}function $(){return T(" ")}function _e(){return T("")}function D(t,e,n,s){return t.addEventListener(e,n,s),()=>t.removeEventListener(e,n,s)}function W(t,e,n){n==null?t.removeAttribute(e):t.getAttribute(e)!==n&&t.setAttribute(e,n)}function We(t){return Array.from(t.childNodes)}function x(t,e){e=""+e,t.data!==e&&(t.data=e)}function K(t,e,n,s){n==null?t.style.removeProperty(e):t.style.setProperty(e,n,"")}let te;function I(t){te=t}const C=[],ie=[];let L=[];const re=[],ke=Promise.resolve();let X=!1;function Te(){X||(X=!0,ke.then(be))}function Y(t){L.push(t)}const z=new Set;let O=0;function be(){if(O!==0)return;const t=te;do{try{for(;O<C.length;){const e=C[O];O++,I(e),He(e.$$)}}catch(e){throw C.length=0,O=0,e}for(I(null),C.length=0,O=0;ie.length;)ie.pop()();for(let e=0;e<L.length;e+=1){const n=L[e];z.has(n)||(z.add(n),n())}L.length=0}while(C.length);for(;re.length;)re.pop()();X=!1,z.clear(),I(t)}function He(t){if(t.fragment!==null){t.update(),B(t.before_update);const e=t.dirty;t.dirty=[-1],t.fragment&&t.fragment.p(t.ctx,e),t.after_update.forEach(Y)}}function Se(t){const e=[],n=[];L.forEach(s=>t.indexOf(s)===-1?e.push(s):n.push(s)),n.forEach(s=>s()),L=e}const G=new Set;let J;function ne(){J={r:0,c:[],p:J}}function se(){J.r||B(J.c),J=J.p}function q(t,e){t&&t.i&&(G.delete(t),t.i(e))}function S(t,e,n,s){if(t&&t.o){if(G.has(t))return;G.add(t),J.c.push(()=>{G.delete(t),s&&(n&&t.d(1),s())}),t.o(e)}else s&&s()}function j(t){return(t==null?void 0:t.length)!==void 0?t:Array.from(t)}function Q(t){t&&t.c()}function N(t,e,n){const{fragment:s,after_update:o}=t.$$;s&&s.m(e,n),Y(()=>{const a=t.$$.on_mount.map(pe).filter(Z);t.$$.on_destroy?t.$$.on_destroy.push(...a):B(a),t.$$.on_mount=[]}),o.forEach(Y)}function F(t,e){const n=t.$$;n.fragment!==null&&(Se(n.after_update),B(n.on_destroy),n.fragment&&n.fragment.d(e),n.on_destroy=n.fragment=null,n.ctx=[])}function $e(t,e){t.$$.dirty[0]===-1&&(C.push(t),Te(),t.$$.dirty.fill(0)),t.$$.dirty[e/31|0]|=1<<e%31}function R(t,e,n,s,o,a,u=null,w=[-1]){const c=te;I(t);const r=t.$$={fragment:null,ctx:[],props:a,update:P,not_equal:o,bound:ae(),on_mount:[],on_destroy:[],on_disconnect:[],before_update:[],after_update:[],context:new Map(e.context||(c?c.$$.context:[])),callbacks:ae(),dirty:w,skip_bound:!1,root:e.target||c.$$.root};u&&u(r.root);let l=!1;if(r.ctx=n?n(t,e.props||{},(d,i,...h)=>{const m=h.length?h[0]:i;return r.ctx&&o(r.ctx[d],r.ctx[d]=m)&&(!r.skip_bound&&r.bound[d]&&r.bound[d](m),l&&$e(t,d)),i}):[],r.update(),l=!0,B(r.before_update),r.fragment=s?s(r.ctx):!1,e.target){if(e.hydrate){const d=We(e.target);r.fragment&&r.fragment.l(d),d.forEach(_)}else r.fragment&&r.fragment.c();e.intro&&q(t.$$.fragment),N(t,e.target,e.anchor),be()}I(c)}class M{constructor(){V(this,"$$");V(this,"$$set")}$destroy(){F(this,1),this.$destroy=P}$on(e,n){if(!Z(n))return P;const s=this.$$.callbacks[e]||(this.$$.callbacks[e]=[]);return s.push(n),()=>{const o=s.indexOf(n);o!==-1&&s.splice(o,1)}}$set(e){this.$$set&&!qe(e)&&(this.$$.skip_bound=!0,this.$$set(e),this.$$.skip_bound=!1)}}const Pe="4";typeof window<"u"&&(window.__svelte||(window.__svelte={v:new Set})).v.add(Pe);const E=[{title:"Java/OOP",subtitle:"Object-Oriented Programming in Java",flashcards:[{question:"What is Encapsulation in Java?",answer:"Encapsulation restricts access to the inner workings of that class using access modifiers."},{question:"What is Inheritance in Java?",answer:"Inheritance is a concept where one class (the subclass or derived class) inherits the fields and methods of another class (the superclass or base class)."},{question:"What is Polymorphism in Java?",answer:"Polymorphism allows methods to perform differently based on the object they are called on."},{question:"What is Abstraction in Java?",answer:"Abstraction hides implementation details and shows only essential features of an object to the outside world."},{question:"How do we achieve abstraction in Java?",answer:"Abstract classes and interfaces"},{question:"What is the difference between public, private, and protected?",answer:`- Public: Accessible from anywhere.
- Private: Accessible only within the same class.
- Protected: Accessible within the same package and by subclasses.`},{question:"What is Overriding in Java?",answer:"Overriding is when a subclass provides a specific implementation for a method already defined in its superclass."},{question:"What is Overloading in Java?",answer:"Overloading is when multiple methods in the same class have the same name but different parameter lists."},{question:"What is the difference between Abstract Class and Interface?",answer:"Abstract classes allow for a mix of abstract and concrete methods, while interfaces only have abstract methods that classes must implement."},{question:"What is garbage collection?",answer:"An automated process to clean up unused memory."}]},{title:"Data Structure",subtitle:"",flashcards:[{question:"What is Array?",answer:"Collection of elements stored in contiguous memory locations."},{question:"What is Linked List?",answer:"Collection of elements where each element points to the next one."},{question:"What is Stack?",answer:"A data structure that follows the Last In, First Out (LIFO) principle."},{question:"What are Stack operations?",answer:`- Push (adds an element to the top of the stack)
- Pop (removes the top element from the stack)`},{question:"What is Queue?",answer:"Data structure that follows the First In, First Out (FIFO) principle"},{question:"What are Queue operations?",answer:`- Enqueue (adding an element to the rear)
- Dequeue (removes the element from the front)`},{question:"What is Tree?",answer:"Data structure consisting of nodes connected by edges. It has a root node, parent nodes, and child node."},{question:"What is a leaf node in Tree?",answer:"A node that does not have any children."},{question:"What are variants of Tree?",answer:"Binary Tree, Binary Search Tree, AVL Tree, Red-Black Tree."},{question:"What is Binary Tree?",answer:"A tree data structure in which each node has at most two children."},{question:"What is Graph?",answer:"A non-linear data structure consisting of nodes connected by edges."},{question:"What is the relationship between Tree and Graph?",answer:"A tree is a specific type of graph characterized by its hierarchical structure without cycles, where each node has a unique parent except for the root node."},{question:"What is Hash Table?",answer:"Data structure that stores key-value pairs, allowing for efficient insertion, deletion, and lookup operations based on a unique hash function."},{question:"What is Collision in Hash Table?",answer:"Where two or more keys generate the same hash value."},{question:"What is Collision Resolution in Hash Table?",answer:"Strategies to manage collisions."},{question:"What are strategies to resolve collision in Hash Table?",answer:"Chaining or open addressing."},{question:"What is Map?",answer:"Data structure that stores unique key-value pairs."},{question:"What is the relationship between Map and Hash Table?",answer:"Hash Table is commonly used to implement Map."}]},{title:"Web Foundation",subtitle:"",flashcards:[{question:"What does HTTP stand for?",answer:"Hypertext Transfer Protocol"},{question:"What is HTTP",answer:"A request-response protocol used for transmitting hypermedia documents."},{question:"What are common HTTP methods?",answer:"GET, POST, PUT, DELETE, PATCH"},{question:"What is HTTP GET method?",answer:"Requests data from a specified resource."},{question:"What is HTTP POST method?",answer:"ubmits data to be processed to a specified resource."},{question:"What is HTTP PUT method?",answer:"pdates a specified resource with new data"},{question:"What is HTTP DELETE method?",answer:"Deletes a specified resource."},{question:"What is HTTP method PATCH?",answer:"Applies partial modifications to a resource."},{question:"What is HTTP status code?",answer:"Numeric code to indicate the outcome of a client's request."},{question:"What does HTTP status code 2xx indicate?",answer:"Success"},{question:"What does HTTP status code 3xx indicate?",answer:"Redirection"},{question:"What does HTTP status code 4xx indicate?",answer:"Client error."},{question:"What does HTTP status code 5xx indicate?",answer:"Server error."},{question:"What does URL stand for?",answer:"Uniform Resource Locator."},{question:"What is URL?",answer:"A address used to access resources on the internet, specifying the location and protocol."},{question:"What does DNS stand for?",answer:"Domain Name System."},{question:"What is DNS?",answer:"It translates domain names (like google.com) into IP addresses (like 172.217.7.238)."}]},{title:"JavaScript/TypeScript",subtitle:"",flashcards:[{question:"What is the relationship between JS and TS?",answer:"TypeScript is a statically typed superset of JavaScript that compiles to plain JavaScript."},{question:"What are arrow functions in JS?",answer:"Arrow functions are a concise way to write functions in JS."},{question:"What is Promise in JS?",answer:"Promises are objects representing the eventual completion or failure of an asynchronous operation. They allow asynchronous code to be written in a more synchronous-like fashion, making it easier to manage."},{question:"What is asynchronous programming in JS?",answer:"Asynchronous programming in JavaScript allows code to execute independently from the main program flow."},{question:"What is a callback function in JS?",answer:"A callback function is a function that is passed as an argument to another function."},{question:"What is the use case of callback function in asynchronous programming in JS?",answer:"Used to handle the results of asynchronous operations once they are completed."},{question:"What is the purpose of the keyword 'async'?",answer:"Used to define asynchronous functions, which return promises."},{question:"What is the purpose of the keyword 'wait'?",answer:"Used inside async functions to wait for and retrieve the result of asynchronous operations, making asynchronous code appear synchronous."},{question:"What is the event loop in JS?",answer:"It manages asynchronous operations by continuously checking the call stack and event queue, ensuring that tasks are executed in a non-blocking manner."},{question:"What is scope in JS?",answer:"Scope refers to the visibility and accessibility of variables."},{question:"How does JS handle errors?",answer:"Using try-catch blocks for synchronous code and catch() methods for asynchronous code"},{question:"What is reduce in JS?",answer:"A higher-order array method used to iterate over an array and accumulate a single result based on a callback function provided by the user."},{question:`What is the output of this code?

const numbers = [1, 2, 3, 4, 5];

const sum = numbers.reduce((accumulator, currentValue) => {
    return accumulator + currentValue;
}, 0);

console.log(sum);`,answer:"15"},{question:"What are the different primitive data types in JS?",answer:"string, number, boolean, bigint, null, undefined, symbol"},{question:"What are the different complex data types in JS?",answer:"object, array, function, map, set"},{question:"What is the difference between == and === operators in JavaScript?",answer:"== is the equality operator that performs type coercion, while === is the strict equality operator that compares both value and type without coercion."},{question:"What is finally in try-catch in JS?",answer:"finally is a block of code used in a try...catch statement. It runs regardless of whether an exception is thrown or caught."}]},{title:"Bootstrap",subtitle:"",flashcards:[{question:"What class is used to style a button with primary theme?",answer:'<button class="btn btn-primary">Primary button</button>'},{question:"What class is used to style a button with secondary theme?",answer:'<button class="btn btn-secondary">Secondary button</button>'},{question:"How do you style an anchor tag as an info-themed button?",answer:'<a href="#" class="btn btn-info">Info anchor tag</a>'},{question:"How do you style an anchor tag as a success-themed button?",answer:'<a href="#" class="btn btn-success">Success anchor tag</a>'},{question:"Which classes are used to create a large danger-themed button?",answer:'<button class="btn btn-lg btn-danger">Large danger button</button>'},{question:"Which classes are used to create a small warning-themed button?",answer:'<button class="btn btn-sm btn-warning">Small warning button</button>'},{question:"How do you create a primary-themed button with an outlined style?",answer:'<button class="btn btn-outline-primary">Outlined button</button>'},{question:"How do you create a large secondary-themed button with an outlined style?",answer:'<button class="btn btn-outline-secondary btn-lg">Large outlined button</button>'},{question:"How do you create a group of buttons with primary, warning, and success themes?",answer:`<div class="btn-group">
  <a href="#" class="btn btn-primary">Button 1</a>
  <a href="#" class="btn btn-warning">Button 2</a>
  <a href="#" class="btn btn-success">Button 3</a>
</div>`},{question:"What class adds a small margin around an element?",answer:'<div class="m-1"></div>'},{question:"What class adds large padding inside an element?",answer:'<div class="p-5"></div>'},{question:"Which classes would you use to add a margin only on the top and bottom of an element?",answer:'<div class="my-3"></div>'},{question:"How do you add a border to an element?",answer:'<div class="border"></div>'},{question:"What class adds a thick red border to the left side of an element?",answer:'<div class="border-start border-danger border-5"></div>'},{question:"How do you make an element’s corners rounded?",answer:'<div class="rounded"></div>'},{question:"Which class adds a small shadow to an element?",answer:'<div class="shadow-sm"></div>'},{question:"How do you make text bold using Bootstrap classes?",answer:'<p class="fw-bold">Bold text</p>'},{question:"What class makes text italic?",answer:'<p class="fst-italic">Italic text</p>'},{question:"Which class adds padding only to the left and right sides of an element?",answer:'<div class="px-3"></div>'},{question:"How do you apply a shadow with a medium size to an element?",answer:'<div class="shadow"></div>'},{question:"How do you apply a font weight of light to text?",answer:'<p class="fw-light">Light text</p>'},{question:"How do you include rounded pill corners on an element?",answer:'<div class="rounded-pill"></div>'},{question:"How do you add a margin to the bottom of an element only?",answer:'<div class="mb-3"></div>'},{question:"What class adds a default border to an element?",answer:'<div class="border"></div>'},{question:"How do you add a top border only to an element?",answer:'<div class="border-top"></div>'},{question:"How do you apply a green border color to the left side of an element?",answer:'<div class="border-start border-success"></div>'},{question:"Which class would you use to add a large shadow to an element?",answer:'<div class="shadow-lg"></div>'},{question:"How do you set a border thickness of 5 on an element?",answer:'<div class="border-5"></div>'},{question:"How do you make text appear bolder than the default bold text?",answer:'<p class="fw-bolder">Bolder text</p>'},{question:"Which class would you use to make text italic and light at the same time?",answer:'<p class="fst-italic fw-light">Italic light text</p>'},{question:"How do you add padding to the start and end of an element?",answer:'<div class="ps-5 pe-5"></div>'},{question:"What class adds a margin on the y-axis (top and bottom) only?",answer:'<div class="my-3"></div>'},{question:"How do you create an element with small padding and a small margin?",answer:'<div class="m-1 p-1"></div>'},{question:"How do you create a bordered element with rounded corners?",answer:'<div class="border rounded"></div>'},{question:"What class would you use to create an element with a default shadow?",answer:'<div class="shadow"></div>'},{question:"How do you apply padding only to the left side of an element?",answer:'<div class="ps-5"></div>'},{question:"How do you apply padding only to the right side of an element?",answer:'<div class="pe-5"></div>'},{question:"How do you add a border to the right side of an element?",answer:'<div class="border-end"></div>'},{question:"How do you create a row in Bootstrap's grid system?",answer:'<div class="row"></div>'},{question:"How do you create a column in Bootstrap's grid system that spans one column width?",answer:'<div class="col"></div>'},{question:"How do you create three equally spaced columns within a row?",answer:`<div class="row">
  <div class="col"><div class="p-5 bg-primary text-light">col 1</div></div>
  <div class="col"><div class="p-5 bg-primary text-light">col 2</div></div>
  <div class="col"><div class="p-5 bg-primary text-light">col 3</div></div>
</div>
`},{question:"How do you set a column to span six grid columns?",answer:'<div class="col-6"></div>'},{question:"How do you create a column that spans 6 columns, another that spans 3, and another that spans 3?",answer:`<div class="row">
  <div class="col-6"><div class="p-5 bg-primary text-light">col 1</div></div>
  <div class="col-3"><div class="p-5 bg-primary text-light">col 2</div></div>
  <div class="col-3"><div class="p-5 bg-primary text-light">col 3</div></div>
</div>
`},{question:"How do you create responsive columns that span 4 columns on small screens and 6 columns on large screens?",answer:'<div class="col-sm-4 col-lg-6"></div>'},{question:"How do you create a row with custom vertical gutter spacing?",answer:'<div class="row gy-3"></div>'},{question:"How do you center a row of columns within a container?",answer:'<div class="row justify-content-center"></div>'},{question:"What class justifies the content at the start of a row?",answer:'<div class="row justify-content-start"></div>'},{question:"What class justifies the content at the end of a row?",answer:'<div class="row justify-content-end"></div>'},{question:"What class distributes columns evenly with space between them?",answer:'<div class="row justify-content-between"></div>'},{question:"How do you distribute columns evenly with space around them?",answer:'<div class="row justify-content-around"></div>'}]}];function xe(t){let e;return{c(){e=T(t[0])},m(n,s){k(n,e,s)},p(n,s){s&1&&x(e,n[0])},d(n){n&&_(e)}}}function Ae(t){let e;return{c(){e=T(t[1])},m(n,s){k(n,e,s)},p(n,s){s&2&&x(e,n[1])},d(n){n&&_(e)}}}function Je(t){let e,n,s=t[3]?"Answer":`Question ${t[2]+1}`,o,a,u,w,c;function r(i,h){return i[3]?Ae:xe}let l=r(t),d=l(t);return{c(){e=y("div"),n=y("div"),o=T(s),a=$(),u=y("div"),d.c(),W(n,"class","question-answer svelte-1c9grjx"),W(u,"class","question-answer-content svelte-1c9grjx"),W(e,"class","flashcard svelte-1c9grjx"),W(e,"role","button"),W(e,"tabindex","0")},m(i,h){k(i,e,h),b(e,n),b(n,o),b(e,a),b(e,u),d.m(u,null),w||(c=[D(e,"click",t[4]),D(e,"keypress",t[4])],w=!0)},p(i,[h]){h&12&&s!==(s=i[3]?"Answer":`Question ${i[2]+1}`)&&x(o,s),l===(l=r(i))&&d?d.p(i,h):(d.d(1),d=l(i),d&&(d.c(),d.m(u,null)))},i:P,o:P,d(i){i&&_(e),d.d(),w=!1,B(c)}}}function Oe(t,e,n){let{question:s}=e,{answer:o}=e,{index:a}=e,u=!1;function w(){u&&n(3,u=!1)}function c(){n(3,u=!u)}return t.$$set=r=>{"question"in r&&n(0,s=r.question),"answer"in r&&n(1,o=r.answer),"index"in r&&n(2,a=r.index)},[s,o,a,u,c,w]}class Ee extends M{constructor(e){super(),R(this,e,Oe,Je,U,{question:0,answer:1,index:2,resetState:5})}get resetState(){return this.$$.ctx[5]}}function le(t,e,n){const s=t.slice();return s[1]=e[n].question,s[2]=e[n].answer,s[4]=n,s}function ce(t){let e,n=t[0].subtitle+"",s;return{c(){e=y("p"),s=T(n),W(e,"class","subtitle svelte-ms8g2g")},m(o,a){k(o,e,a),b(e,s)},p(o,a){a&1&&n!==(n=o[0].subtitle+"")&&x(s,n)},d(o){o&&_(e)}}}function ue(t){let e,n;return e=new Ee({props:{question:t[1],answer:t[2],index:t[4]}}),{c(){Q(e.$$.fragment)},m(s,o){N(e,s,o),n=!0},p(s,o){const a={};o&1&&(a.question=s[1]),o&1&&(a.answer=s[2]),e.$set(a)},i(s){n||(q(e.$$.fragment,s),n=!0)},o(s){S(e.$$.fragment,s),n=!1},d(s){F(e,s)}}}function Ce(t){let e,n,s=t[0].title+"",o,a,u,w,c=t[0].subtitle.length>0&&ce(t),r=j(t[0].flashcards),l=[];for(let i=0;i<r.length;i+=1)l[i]=ue(le(t,r,i));const d=i=>S(l[i],1,1,()=>{l[i]=null});return{c(){e=y("div"),n=y("h1"),o=T(s),a=$(),c&&c.c(),u=$();for(let i=0;i<l.length;i+=1)l[i].c();W(n,"class","svelte-ms8g2g")},m(i,h){k(i,e,h),b(e,n),b(n,o),b(e,a),c&&c.m(e,null),b(e,u);for(let m=0;m<l.length;m+=1)l[m]&&l[m].m(e,null);w=!0},p(i,[h]){if((!w||h&1)&&s!==(s=i[0].title+"")&&x(o,s),i[0].subtitle.length>0?c?c.p(i,h):(c=ce(i),c.c(),c.m(e,u)):c&&(c.d(1),c=null),h&1){r=j(i[0].flashcards);let m;for(m=0;m<r.length;m+=1){const H=le(i,r,m);l[m]?(l[m].p(H,h),q(l[m],1)):(l[m]=ue(H),l[m].c(),q(l[m],1),l[m].m(e,null))}for(ne(),m=r.length;m<l.length;m+=1)d(m);se()}},i(i){if(!w){for(let h=0;h<r.length;h+=1)q(l[h]);w=!0}},o(i){l=l.filter(Boolean);for(let h=0;h<l.length;h+=1)S(l[h]);w=!1},d(i){i&&_(e),c&&c.d(),ee(l,i)}}}function Le(t,e,n){let{topic:s}=e;return t.$$set=o=>{"topic"in o&&n(0,s=o.topic)},[s]}class je extends M{constructor(e){super(),R(this,e,Le,Ce,U,{topic:0})}}function de(t,e,n){const s=t.slice();return s[5]=e[n],s}function he(t){let e,n=t[5].label+"",s,o,a,u;function w(){return t[4](t[5])}return{c(){e=y("button"),s=T(n),o=$(),W(e,"class","dropdown-item svelte-1mmmvwn")},m(c,r){k(c,e,r),b(e,s),b(e,o),a||(u=D(e,"click",w),a=!0)},p(c,r){t=c,r&2&&n!==(n=t[5].label+"")&&x(s,n)},d(c){c&&_(e),a=!1,u()}}}function Be(t){let e,n,s,o,a,u,w,c=j(t[1]),r=[];for(let l=0;l<c.length;l+=1)r[l]=he(de(t,c,l));return{c(){e=y("div"),n=y("button"),s=T(t[0]),o=$(),a=y("div");for(let l=0;l<r.length;l+=1)r[l].c();W(n,"class","dropdown-button svelte-1mmmvwn"),W(a,"class","dropdown-content svelte-1mmmvwn"),K(a,"display",t[2]?"block":"none"),W(e,"class","dropdown svelte-1mmmvwn")},m(l,d){k(l,e,d),b(e,n),b(n,s),b(e,o),b(e,a);for(let i=0;i<r.length;i+=1)r[i]&&r[i].m(a,null);u||(w=D(n,"click",t[3]),u=!0)},p(l,[d]){if(d&1&&x(s,l[0]),d&6){c=j(l[1]);let i;for(i=0;i<c.length;i+=1){const h=de(l,c,i);r[i]?r[i].p(h,d):(r[i]=he(h),r[i].c(),r[i].m(a,null))}for(;i<r.length;i+=1)r[i].d(1);r.length=c.length}d&4&&K(a,"display",l[2]?"block":"none")},i:P,o:P,d(l){l&&_(e),ee(r,l),u=!1,w()}}}function Ie(t,e,n){let{label:s}=e,{items:o}=e,a=!1;function u(){n(2,a=!a)}const w=c=>{c.onClick(),n(2,a=!1)};return t.$$set=c=>{"label"in c&&n(0,s=c.label),"items"in c&&n(1,o=c.items)},[s,o,a,u,w]}class De extends M{constructor(e){super(),R(this,e,Ie,Be,U,{label:0,items:1})}}function Ne(t){let e,n,s,o;return{c(){e=y("button"),n=T(t[0]),W(e,"class","svelte-1bual08")},m(a,u){k(a,e,u),b(e,n),s||(o=D(e,"click",function(){Z(t[1])&&t[1].apply(this,arguments)}),s=!0)},p(a,[u]){t=a,u&1&&x(n,t[0])},i:P,o:P,d(a){a&&_(e),s=!1,o()}}}function Fe(t,e,n){let{label:s}=e,{onClick:o}=e;return t.$$set=a=>{"label"in a&&n(0,s=a.label),"onClick"in a&&n(1,o=a.onClick)},[s,o]}class Ue extends M{constructor(e){super(),R(this,e,Fe,Ne,U,{label:0,onClick:1})}}function fe(t,e,n){const s=t.slice();return s[2]=e[n],s[4]=n,s}function me(t){let e,n;return e=new je({props:{topic:t[2]}}),{c(){Q(e.$$.fragment)},m(s,o){N(e,s,o),n=!0},i(s){n||(q(e.$$.fragment,s),n=!0)},o(s){S(e.$$.fragment,s),n=!1},d(s){F(e,s)}}}function we(t){let e,n,s=t[0]===t[4]&&me(t);return{c(){s&&s.c(),e=_e()},m(o,a){s&&s.m(o,a),k(o,e,a),n=!0},p(o,a){o[0]===o[4]?s?a&1&&q(s,1):(s=me(o),s.c(),q(s,1),s.m(e.parentNode,e)):s&&(ne(),S(s,1,1,()=>{s=null}),se())},i(o){n||(q(s),n=!0)},o(o){S(s),n=!1},d(o){o&&_(e),s&&s.d(o)}}}function Re(t){let e,n,s,o,a,u,w,c=E[t[0]].flashcards.length+"",r,l,d,i,h,m;n=new De({props:{label:"Select Topic",items:E.map(t[1])}});let H=j(E),p=[];for(let f=0;f<H.length;f+=1)p[f]=we(fe(t,H,f));const ge=f=>S(p[f],1,1,()=>{p[f]=null});return h=new Ue({props:{label:"Scroll to Top",onClick:Me}}),{c(){e=y("div"),Q(n.$$.fragment),s=$(),o=y("div"),a=$(),u=y("div"),w=T("Number of Flashcards: "),r=T(c),l=$();for(let f=0;f<p.length;f+=1)p[f].c();d=$(),i=y("div"),Q(h.$$.fragment),K(o,"margin-right","20px"),W(e,"class","control-box svelte-1lj0z4k")},m(f,g){k(f,e,g),N(n,e,null),b(e,s),b(e,o),b(e,a),b(e,u),b(u,w),b(u,r),k(f,l,g);for(let A=0;A<p.length;A+=1)p[A]&&p[A].m(f,g);k(f,d,g),k(f,i,g),N(h,i,null),m=!0},p(f,[g]){const A={};if(g&1&&(A.items=E.map(f[1])),n.$set(A),(!m||g&1)&&c!==(c=E[f[0]].flashcards.length+"")&&x(r,c),g&1){H=j(E);let v;for(v=0;v<H.length;v+=1){const oe=fe(f,H,v);p[v]?(p[v].p(oe,g),q(p[v],1)):(p[v]=we(oe),p[v].c(),q(p[v],1),p[v].m(d.parentNode,d))}for(ne(),v=H.length;v<p.length;v+=1)ge(v);se()}},i(f){if(!m){q(n.$$.fragment,f);for(let g=0;g<H.length;g+=1)q(p[g]);q(h.$$.fragment,f),m=!0}},o(f){S(n.$$.fragment,f),p=p.filter(Boolean);for(let g=0;g<p.length;g+=1)S(p[g]);S(h.$$.fragment,f),m=!1},d(f){f&&(_(e),_(l),_(d),_(i)),F(n),ee(p,f),F(h)}}}function Me(){window.scrollTo({top:0,behavior:"smooth"})}function Ge(t,e,n){let s=0;return[s,(a,u)=>({label:a.title,onClick:()=>{n(0,s=u)}})]}class Qe extends M{constructor(e){super(),R(this,e,Ge,Re,U,{})}}new Qe({target:document.getElementById("app")});
